I got one.
You'll do.
All right.
Fresh as it comes.
Down you go.
You can stop dancing out.
Should be enough.
These things are hard to catch.
Stay down.
No.
Save these for the trail.
That's her.
She's coming for us.
Make it.
I'll finish you.
Oh,
got another shot for you.
Wanna play here?
Sure.
Forget about travelling light.
No
rain.
Well, mostly waterproof.
No.
Yeah.
No,
No.
Yeah.
OK, Alarm's down.
No.
Me?
Yeah.
You.
You
still sniffing around?
They've taken those travellers captive.
I'll get this open.
Hold on.
It's all right.
I'm getting you out.
No.
Okay.
Not too much already.
We need warriors like her Ready to stand up for the Sunday
crazy.
Awesome to kill our son.
Nor was there to protect her son.
We will never be able to repay you for the life of our son.
Less
you?
Nothing to prepare.
This must be sensed.
A rock.
It's being attacked by machines.
I don't like her chances.
You wanna tell wardens your navel down?
Let's take our chances.
Behemoth Strong against Shaq.
Great holders.
Destroying this component will detach the cargo container.
Freeze canister forced loader.
Destroying this component disables the lifting attacks.
Power cell.
Don't.
Three.
You pulled us out of a tough spot.
Outlander.
Welcome to Sunstone Rock.
You should speak toward in Geneva.
Inside.
Yeah.
What
should
by the sun?
It's over
here.
It wasn't to lure.
You don't know how they got it.
Rob Gun fell apart on his person.
No doubt we searched him.
How?
You don't want to know how?
Always stay bright.
Always tailored.
That's what I say,
Warden.
Geneva.
This is the one who defeated the behemoths.
Outlander?
I'm impressed.
I don't impress easily.
Tell me, how do you fare with hunting?
Living prey?
I haven't had any complaints.
Why?
Three dangerous prisoners have escaped.
I need my men here getting the others back in line.
None of this would have happened if we dealt with criminals the old way, but have clashed that going before.
And here I am.
And here you are.
What's the old way to be buried up to the neck and left for the sun's judgement?
Seems to me like the judgment's already been made.
Not one of them committed another crime.
So the card to keep their criminals in this place.
Since the liberation, we've had them all from thieves to the mad King.
Geron's former Kestral Sze the Sun King believes in the power of change.
And sure enough, some did change shed their skin like lizards.
I thought all criminals were the same once.
That's why the Sun King gave me command of Sunstone Rock as an education.
Sounds like an honour.
I mean, I haven't seen any other women encourage arm No, I'm not one of your sisters.
No woman can wear card your armour.
When I was young, I chose to become a soldier one good enough to join a VOD honour guard.
There was talk about what I waas.
So I'd say Test me Then I'll break your arm after enough arms have been broken.
There was less talk.
I'm curious, but I'd rather we didn't have to start fighting.
Agreed.
So you want these prisoners brought back?
No.
I want them put in the earth.
I doubt they'll give you any choice.
They had their chance with the Sun King's generosity.
So now they face mine A bounty on all their heads.
Who are these dangerous prisoners?
Three from the isolation cages.
Don't feel sorry for them.
They've lived well off the Sun King's conscience.
First, his Roz Grand Awesome trap maker hates the Kharja.
Crazy as a loon in heat.
God in one too many blasts or one too few.
Then there's Julia, a two knocked warrior.
If that means anything to you, not really another tribe.
Rivers from the south bloodthirsty.
Some say they're cannibals, but she slurped Greul well enough.
And the last is given a traitor who smuggled weapons to the exiles.
Compared to the other two, this one doesn't seem so bad.
He helped drag out a civil war.
All for these shards that got him.
A machine has more warmth.
If I did this for you, I need a lead on them.
Well, when Julia first swept through the Sunday, um, it was with the jungle bandits.
I say she'll go back.
Roz Grand.
We pulled out of a crack in dust Mesa, where he'd been tinkering with his bombs and given will be trying to pay his way across the lake.
I'd burn my palm on it.
Looking bright market.
Yeah,
I need them soon enough.
Okay.
I already got rid of the bandits.
I didn't think it would be hard to find this warrior.
I tell you, they would come drive her into the dirt.
No way!
We could have talked about this.
Huh?
All the cards you did was talk.
Talk?
Please talk and shackle me.
Do you?
We fought like to knock.
I'd have taken you for my child.
You can't just take a child.
A strong take from the weak, weak and in the taking I'm a stronger the storeys pricked into my skin.
Look,
Children, riches, lives.
And
all of these have been mine.
Drink of my not my blood and live on,
huh?
No,
I've got enough storeys to carry.
Did she really save the Sun King?
Nora?
Too much.
Ossa.
Rahm influenced the palace.
What's he thinking?
Letting
crazy.
Awesome.
Tried to kill our son
from Missy Mandel to Mark Oslo.
Subject what scares me.
Merck.
Remember what I told you in my last message about how scared I am?
Well, I figured out what scares me, and it's not the bots.
I mean, yeah, they're horrifying.
But when we finally come face to face, I ll either live or die.
And the starkness and simplicity of that winery is well reassuring.
What scares me is how much I like this.
How do you feel?
It's in my hands.
The kick of a coil gun Jesus, Merck.
We lived in a squat for three years, matching Mohawks.
Spend our days throbbing off Razor wing or Duster Night's thrashing off Slam Fun Cakes Way were goddamn anarchists.
And now this.
This discipline jargon uniforms and I like it.
That's what terrifies me, Mark, no crisp, reassuring finery.
Here I'm loving what I hate or hated.
So does that mean my entire life was just opposed?
Or that the person I wass is already dead?
I don't know, I tried to tell myself It's a different kind of war survival, not profits.
I try to tell myself it's just a different kind of direct action.
I mean, what are the box?
If not the ultimate capitalist stooge is right.
But thinking just tyres me out.
All I know is we've got to fight until zero Don is ready.
If I end up surviving this, guess I can worry about my politics, then love to you and, little said, is he